<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="4.0.0">Jekyll</generator><link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="http://localhost:4000/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2020-03-26T12:38:19-06:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Borderland Food Company</title><subtitle>&lt;strong&gt;Simple Small Batches.&lt;/strong&gt; We ensure that our bone broth is simmered low and slow to maximize the nutrients extracted during the cooking process. </subtitle><entry><title type="html">Looking For Ways To Boost Your Immunity? Try Bone Broth!</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/2020/03/16/boost-immunity.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Looking For Ways To Boost Your Immunity? Try Bone Broth!" /><published>2020-03-16T06:01:35-06:00</published><updated>2020-03-16T06:01:35-06:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/2020/03/16/boost-immunity</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/2020/03/16/boost-immunity.html">&lt;p&gt;There’s no denying that there is a lot of focus on healthy immunity right now, and for very good reason. Our immune system is our body’s last line of defence in keeping us healthy and fighting infection so that we can in turn keep those around us healthy. In this blog post, we’re going to give you a brief overview of what our immune system actually is and what it does. We’ll also discuss ways for you to improve your immune system and how bone broth is a fantastic way of achieving a strong immune system.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;One thing we want to drive home: while our immune systems are at the forefront of our minds right now, we cannot stress enough how important it is to take care of this aspect of our health year round! By ensuring our immunity is in it’s optimal state and by taking proactive steps to help build strong immune systems, we’re not only doing ourselves a huge service- we’re doing a service for our families, our coworkers and our communities. If we’re learning one thing right now, it’s that individual health is community health! We are all connected and we’re all in this together.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/celebration-cheers-dining-1268558.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;dining cheers&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;what-exactly-is-our-immune-system-what-does-it-do&quot;&gt;What exactly is our immune system? What does it do?&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Our immune system is made up of a collection of structures and processes within the body to protect against disease and infection. When our immune system is functioning optimally, it will identify harmful viruses, bacteria and parasites, and can distinguish these invaders from our body’s normal healthy tissue.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;what-is-the-connection-between-the-gut-and-our-immune-system&quot;&gt;What is the connection between the gut and our immune system?&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;What might surprise you is that it turns out that around 70 percent of the immune system lives in the gut! So, as you can imagine, keeping our gut lining as healthy as possible is the best way to ensure that we keep our immune systems strong. If our gut lining is healthy, the entire gut environment is able to function more optimally. This means that the healthy gut bacteria can do their jobs! And it turns out they have a very important job when it comes to immunity. The healthy gut bacteria (or biome) in the gut help your immune system’s T cells develop. T cells are responsible for attacking foreign substances in our bodies, so the health of these cells is vital. The health of our gut biome is extremely important as it will impact our immune system’s ability to respond correctly to these foreign invaders.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/DSCF7503.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;bone broth in arms&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;how-can-we-improve-the-health-of-our-gut-and-immune-system&quot;&gt;How can we improve the health of our gut and immune system?&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Science has shown that healthy habits like lowering our stress levels, getting enough sleep, and exercising regularly are all things that will improve the health of our gut biome along with taking probitiotics and eating fermented foods (kimchi, sauerkraut, kombucha). Ensuring we have a healthy gut biome is one thing, but we also have to ensure that this biome has a healthy place to live, in a stable environment so that it can flourish and boost our immunity and overall health.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In order to provide our helpful gut bacteria with this healthy environment, we need to ensure that we have a healthy, sealed gut lining. When the gut isn’t sealed, it can lead to leaky gut syndrome and this negatively impacts our biome’s ability to do it’s best work.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;how-does-bone-broth-help-to-improve-our-immune-systems&quot;&gt;How does bone broth help to improve our immune systems?&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The nutrients in bone broth are fantastic at healing the gut and allowing our gut’s biome to do it’s best work. Collagen and glucosamine are plentiful in bone broth and are vital in helping to seal our intestinal barrier and improving our immune system’s ability to fight virus’s. Bone broth is one of the simplest ways of supplementing collagen and glucosamine in our diets! Bone broth is easy to digest, easy to prepare (just thaw and sip!) and is especially comforting. Best of all, it can be delivered directly to your door!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Keep in mind that bone broth is like brushing your teeth- it has to become a part of your daily habits in order to see the best benefits. We recommend consuming one cup of bone broth per day for optimal benefits.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;wondering-where-to-buy-bone-broth&quot;&gt;Wondering where to buy bone broth?&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You can find our bone broth in the freezer section of many retailers near you, just click here. Alternatively, our bone broths are also available for delivery to your door at spud.ca and trulocal.ca&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/IMG_7858.jpeg&quot; alt=&quot;bone broth and drink&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">There’s no denying that there is a lot of focus on healthy immunity right now, and for very good reason. Our immune system is our body’s last line of defence in keeping us healthy and fighting infection so that we can in turn keep those around us healthy. In this blog post, we’re going to give you a brief overview of what our immune system actually is and what it does. We’ll also discuss ways for you to improve your immune system and how bone broth is a fantastic way of achieving a strong immune system.</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="http://localhost:4000/BL_0117.jpg" /><media:content medium="image" url="http://localhost:4000/BL_0117.jpg" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" /></entry><entry><title type="html">Collagen - It’s Nature’s Botox!</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/2020/02/05/collagen-natures-botox.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Collagen - It's Nature's Botox!" /><published>2020-02-05T05:01:35-07:00</published><updated>2020-02-05T05:01:35-07:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/2020/02/05/collagen-natures-botox</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/2020/02/05/collagen-natures-botox.html">&lt;p&gt;Let’s be real. We all wish we could slow the hands of time. For some of us, this is especially true when it comes to the appearance of our skin! One of the ways that we’re improving our skin naturally is through the use of collagen. The anti-aging effects of collagen is one of the major benefits of bone broth. You may have heard that collagen is good for your hair skin and nails, but how exactly does it help? And does the science support it? In this blog post, we answer both of these questions and show you why collagen is basically nature’s botox.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/photo2.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;chicken noodle soup&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;what-is-collagen&quot;&gt;What is collagen?&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Simply put, collagen is a protein! It’s the most abundant protein in our bodies and it’s responsible for holding our connective tissues together, including our skin! Collagen is the protein that gives our skin elasticity, and is also a major player in our  hair and nail health as well! Collagen is made up of two amino acids- glycine and proline.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As we get older, the amount of collagen that our bodies produce slows down, which is why we start to see fine lines, less elasticity and an overall less “plump” appearance to our skin. This slow down in collagen production varies between individuals but can start as early as our late 20’s! There are many factors that determine the age at which the collagen production slows down, among which are genetic factors, alcohol intake, sun exposure, and diet!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Given this information, it’s no surprise that collagen is the top priority for many when it comes to battling the aging process!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/IMG_1469.jpeg&quot; alt=&quot;turkey bone broth&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;what-does-science-say&quot;&gt;What does science say?&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Lucky for us, there have been multiple studies which examine the efficacy of oral collagen supplementation on our skin! Science tells us that increasing collagen intake can improve the appearance of our skin by decreasing fine lines, improving elasticity, and improving hydration. There has even been a systematic review examining collagen’s impact on our skin! (A systematic review is a thorough examination of a whole bunch of research, and is pretty much the pinnacle of research!)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Suffice it to say, scientific research has shown collagen to be very helpful when it comes to slowing down and even reversing the ageing process!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/IMG_1555.jpeg&quot; alt=&quot;smoothie booster bone broth&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;how-do-i-get-these-incredible-health-and-skin-benefits&quot;&gt;How do I get these incredible health and skin benefits?&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Collagen is only found in animal proteins, and the simplest way of dramatically increasing your collagen intake is to incorporate bone broth into your diet! When animal bones are boiled over a long period time, as they are when making bone broth, the collagen that’s hiding in the cartilage is extracted! This leaves us with a nutrient rich broth, full of collagen- it’s basically youth in a bottle!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To find out where to buy bone broth, click here! For recipes and more information, read our other blogs!&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Let’s be real. We all wish we could slow the hands of time. For some of us, this is especially true when it comes to the appearance of our skin! One of the ways that we’re improving our skin naturally is through the use of collagen. The anti-aging effects of collagen is one of the major benefits of bone broth. You may have heard that collagen is good for your hair skin and nails, but how exactly does it help? And does the science support it? In this blog post, we answer both of these questions and show you why collagen is basically nature’s botox.</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="http://localhost:4000/flowers-skin.jpg" /><media:content medium="image" url="http://localhost:4000/flowers-skin.jpg" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" /></entry><entry><title type="html">Healthy Creamy Cauliflower Soup</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/2020/01/13/cauliflower-soup.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Healthy Creamy Cauliflower Soup" /><published>2020-01-13T05:01:35-07:00</published><updated>2020-01-13T05:01:35-07:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/2020/01/13/cauliflower-soup</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/2020/01/13/cauliflower-soup.html">&lt;p&gt;Alright. You’re well in to your New Years resolution for 2020! Whether you resolved to do better for your health or not…. this recipe will blow your socks off. This creamy cauliflower soup is so incredibly clean, you’ll find it hard to believe that it suits any diet! Keto, Whole30, Paleo, or just plain old balanced eating- you cannot go wrong with this recipe.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/IMG_1654.jpeg&quot; alt=&quot;chopped vegetables&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Before we skip right to the “how to”, let’s review why it’s so important to choose bone broth for the base! There are so many incredible benefits to bone broth because it contains amazing nutrients! From collagen to calcium, magnesium and phosphorous, bone broth packs a punch. Those shelf stable soup stocks? They are essentially void of nutrition!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/IMG_1779.jpeg&quot; alt=&quot;pot filled with vegetables&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The nutrients in bone broth help us to be at the top of our game both physically and mentally! The chicken bone broth in this recipe not only adds amazing flavour, but will improve gut health, joint health, AND skin, hair and nail health. PLUS it makes this recipe super filling, which is great for weight loss. Wondering where to buy bone broth? Click here to find the nearest retailer and be sure to look in the freezer section! When it comes to bone broth, frozen is freshest.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/IMG_1874.jpeg&quot; alt=&quot;creamy cauliflower soup&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;creamy-cauliflower-soup&quot;&gt;CREAMY CAULIFLOWER SOUP&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Ingredients:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;1 tablespoon olive oil or coconut oil&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;1 large carrot, peeled and diced&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;2 celery stalks, diced&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;1 medium onion, diced&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;3 cloves garlic, minced&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;1 head cauliflower, roughly chopped&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;1 medium potato, peeled and roughly chopped (optional for keto/paleo)&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;4 cups Borderland Food Co chicken bone broth&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;1 cup coconut milk&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Salt and pepper&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Directions:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;1) Heat olive oil in a large pot. Add carrot, celery and onion and cook for 2-3 minutes.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;2) Add the garlic, cauliflower and potato to the pot, stir occasionally until veggies soften (about 5 minutes).&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;3) Add chicken bone broth and bring to a boil, then turn down to a simmer. Allow to simmer until all ingredients are tender, then remove from heat.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;4) Add coconut milk and blend with an immersion blender. Add salt and pepper to taste. Serve warm and top with grated cheddar cheese (optional).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/IMG_1724.jpeg&quot; alt=&quot;pot filled with vegetables&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Alright. You’re well in to your New Years resolution for 2020! Whether you resolved to do better for your health or not…. this recipe will blow your socks off. This creamy cauliflower soup is so incredibly clean, you’ll find it hard to believe that it suits any diet! Keto, Whole30, Paleo, or just plain old balanced eating- you cannot go wrong with this recipe.</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="http://localhost:4000/IMG_1604.jpeg" /><media:content medium="image" url="http://localhost:4000/IMG_1604.jpeg" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" /></entry><entry><title type="html">Top 10 Reasons To Add Bone Broth To Your Daily Routine</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/2019/10/10/top-10-reasons.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Top 10 Reasons To Add Bone Broth To Your Daily Routine" /><published>2019-10-10T06:01:35-06:00</published><updated>2019-10-10T06:01:35-06:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/2019/10/10/top-10-reasons</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/2019/10/10/top-10-reasons.html">&lt;p&gt;Still not sure what all the hype is about bone broth? Well, we’re here to fill you in on the top ten reasons that we think it is more than worth your while to add it to your daily routine. At Borderland Food Co., we make it easy to be able to incorporate bone broth into your daily routine. With Canada’s largest variety of flavours and a taste-free smoothie booster, we know that this is a healthy habit you can keep!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/IMG_0565.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;vegetables on cutting board&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;1. It’s soooooo nutritious!&lt;/strong&gt; Nutrients in bone broth are highly bioavailable and don’t require a lot of effort to be absorbed by our cells. Did you catch that?? Minimal effort! Your body will thank you.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;2. It makes your joints feel smoother than that pick up line you once fell for from that unemployed dude on Tinder.&lt;/strong&gt; Remember? A few years back? That guy who “forgot his wallet” on your first date?? Don’t wanna talk about it? Okay, then let’s talk about broth. Bone broth contains chondroitin sulfate and glucosamine, the compounds sold as pricey supplements to reduce inflammation, arthritis and joint pain. We’re not getting any younger! Let’s take care of those joints.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;3. It heals your leaky gut!&lt;/strong&gt; And let’s face it. The only thing less appealing than the phrase “leaky gut” is an actual leaky gut. But hey, the gelatin in bone broth protects and heals the mucosal lining of the digestive tract and aids in more effective digestion of nutrients! Good-bye leaky gut, hello beautiful healthy mucosa!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;4. It gets those toxins out!&lt;/strong&gt; The liver wasn’t built to withstand the amount of toxins and chemicals that we regularly pump into our bodies in today’s world (plus, we all like to partake in a nice gallon of vino every now and again, amitirite?!). The good news: bone broth contains TONS of glycine, aka the liver’s side kick and bestie when it comes to getting rid of evil, nasty toxins. 
Pro-tip: bone broth also knows how to pull its weight when it comes to fighting hangovers due to these detoxing effects! Stop judging us… this pro-tip comes from years of “field research”.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;5. It supports hair growth and helps to keep your nails strong and your skin young!&lt;/strong&gt; That’s right. You can continue to celebrate your annual 27th birthday and no one will be the wiser. The collagen and gelatin in bone broth help to improve the appearance of your skin, hair, and nails… for a fraction of the price you’d pay for any beauty treatment, we might add.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/22046PM.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;wavy hair&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;6. It promotes sleep and calms the mind.&lt;/strong&gt; Bone broth? More like ohm broth! The glycine found in bone broth can be very calming. You’ll sleep like a baby. (A beautiful baby with fantastic hair, skin and nails, and an impermeable mucosa).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;7. It’s weight loss friendly!&lt;/strong&gt; Bone broth is super low in calories, high in nutrients, and the gelatin that’s naturally present in the broth helps us to feel full. We could all use a lil’ help with portion control… this is an easy and yummy way to do it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;8. It decreases inflammation!&lt;/strong&gt; Bone broth also contains large amounts of the amino acids glycine and proline, both of which are extremely anti-inflammatory.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;9. It fights infections!&lt;/strong&gt; The amino acids that are found in bone broth have been shown to boost immunity. Turns out your grandma got it right when she forced bone broth on you whenever you were sick with any possible illness. Thanks grams!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;10. BECAUSE WE SAID SO AND SO DID YOUR GRANDMA.&lt;/strong&gt; If the above information was not enough to convince you that the broth is worth adding to your daily routine, then hot damn you’re difficult to please. BUT, we encourage you to try it anyways. It tastes delicious, there’s a million and one ways to use it, and we know that you wont regret the health benefits. Chances are, you can find Borderland Food Co bone broths in a retailer near you.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Happy sipping!!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/BL_0226.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;chocolate smoothie&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Still not sure what all the hype is about bone broth? Well, we’re here to fill you in on the top ten reasons that we think it is more than worth your while to add it to your daily routine. At Borderland Food Co., we make it easy to be able to incorporate bone broth into your daily routine. With Canada’s largest variety of flavours and a taste-free smoothie booster, we know that this is a healthy habit you can keep!</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="http://localhost:4000/DSCF7383.jpg" /><media:content medium="image" url="http://localhost:4000/DSCF7383.jpg" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" /></entry><entry><title type="html">Top 5 Ways To Use Bone Broth That Will Blow Your Mind!</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/2019/07/29/top-5-ways-to-use-bone-broth.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Top 5 Ways To Use Bone Broth That Will Blow Your Mind!" /><published>2019-07-29T09:05:55-06:00</published><updated>2019-07-29T09:05:55-06:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/2019/07/29/top-5-ways-to-use-bone-broth</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/2019/07/29/top-5-ways-to-use-bone-broth.html">&lt;p&gt;Ok. I’m going to open by saying that if you have only been sipping bone broth straight up or using it in the conventional ways (soups, stews and chilli), then you have been mega big time missing out and you’re about to thank me!
Listen up. Bone broth is amazing. But, who the heck wants to sip hot bone broth or make a winter comfort food in the middle of the gaddang summer?! NO ONE DOES. But we still want the amazing health benefits of the delicious superfood. What to do.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This age old conundrum is why we’ve created Canada’s only tasteless bone broth! We call it a Smoothie Booster, but it can be used for so much more than smoothies! Ready to have your horizons expanded?! Here we go:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;1. Smoothie bowls.&lt;/strong&gt; Ok, let’s get the obvious one out of the way. Adding the smoothie booster to smoothies and smoothie bowls…. you can do the math on that one. Lots of collagen that’s super easy for your body to absorb? You betcha. Toss it in there.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/IMG_0433.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;smoothie bowl&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;2. Popsicles!&lt;/strong&gt; Whether they’re for you or your kids, blend up some Borderland Smoothie Booster with some fruit and honey, pour in to a popsicle mold, wait a few hours, and you’ve got yourself a delicious, nutritious summer snack. Check out a more detailed “how to” here!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/IMG_0545.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;popsicle&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;3. Hot Chocolate.&lt;/strong&gt; Follow our recipe here to make your own collagen rich, guilt free hot chocolate. The perfect bedtime sippin’ bevie!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/IMG_7858.jpeg&quot; alt=&quot;hot chocolate&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;4. Oatmeal.&lt;/strong&gt; Get your shot of bone broth first thing in the morning in your oats! Cook your oatmeal in our smoothie booster rather than water and voila! Added health benefits before you’re even out the door.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/oatmeal.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;oatmeal&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;5. Fruit leather.&lt;/strong&gt; Remember fruit roll ups and fruit by the foot?! Sooooo yummy but also soooooo sugary. Well, we’ve put our evil minds to good use to come up with a way to turn those sugary childhood lunchbox treats into healthier options with the added health benefits of bone broth! Follow us on social media to see when we drop that beauty of a recipe!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/How-to-Make-Fruit-Leather-14.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;fruit leather&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;That’s it folks! With our unique smoothie booster, we no longer have any excuses to not be including bone broth in our every day diets. It’s SO EASY!&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Ok. I’m going to open by saying that if you have only been sipping bone broth straight up or using it in the conventional ways (soups, stews and chilli), then you have been mega big time missing out and you’re about to thank me! Listen up. Bone broth is amazing. But, who the heck wants to sip hot bone broth or make a winter comfort food in the middle of the gaddang summer?! NO ONE DOES. But we still want the amazing health benefits of the delicious superfood. What to do.</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="http://localhost:4000/IMG_0458.jpg" /><media:content medium="image" url="http://localhost:4000/IMG_0458.jpg" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" /></entry></feed>